hulala.com.my 2014-06-26

# Best daily deals in Klang Valley, group discounts, vouchers and everyday deals in Malaysia, Up to 90% discounts! - Hulala.com.my

**This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for the Hulala website (collectively, the "website" is located at www.hulala.com.my).**

Hulala Malaysia, the provider of the Website (referred to as "us" or "we"), is committed to protecting your privacy online. Please read the following to learn how we handle your personal information and what information we collect from you (the "User" or the "End User"). It applies generally to our subsidiaries, joint venture and strategic partner websites whose specific privacy available from Privacy pages. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please email us.

Your privacy information are important to us.

##  General Practices

We need it when we really need it to proceed certain transaction which requires some of you privacy information or reference purposes.

We provide a set of consistent privacy practices in office, out of the office, subsidaries, joint venture and strategic partners.

We don't share your personal information with anyone except due to the redemption of your Vouchers, notification, verification, comply with the law, product announcement or protect our rights.

We don't store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

## Collection

You can browse this website without revealing who you are and we do not collect any personal information if you only visit this website.

When we do collect personal information, it' usually directly from you and you are consent or authorize us to transfer or storage of that information to our data center in Malaysia. Therefore, you are no longer anonymous to us. We start receiving your personal information when you join as a member and when you place an order with us.

We may collect the following information :   
Your name, financial information such as credit card or bank account numbers strictly on your transaction purposes, postal address, telephone number, email address.   
Your community discussions and correspondence.   
Cookies, Web log, IP addresss and supplemental information from third parties. 

## Authorized Third Party Service Providers

All Online payments are handled by ipay88 an external third party service providers. We strictly do not wish view or store your credit card or banking details when you are doing you transaction. If you need more information about ipay88 please visit the [www.ipay88.com](http://www.ipay88.com/) website for details of their privacy policies and security measures.

## Marketing Purposes

We simply do not resell or rent your personal information to third parties on any offers for their marketing purposes without your clear consent. When we use, we only use your personal information for the purposes for which you give it to us and for internal management purposes. We may send daily, weekly, monthly newsletters or deals information via [reminder@news.hulala.com.my](mailto:reminder@news.hulala.com.my) (Hulala MY) based on your information such as email addresses or mobile that you provide to us. If you do not wish to receive promotional or other marketing material from us, please let us know and we will proceed with your request (you can simply un-tick certain receiving information preferences in your hulala account) or unsubscribe via the link which is located at the top newsletter that you received.

## Personal Data Protection Notice 

With acquiescence to the Personal Data Protection Act 2010 and its guidelines, this notice is issued to all our respected customers and/or prospective customers, informing you of your rights concerning your personal data that has been and/or will be, collected and processed by us.

  1. **Compilation and processing of personal data**
    * We have collected and will collect your personal data to be processed by us and/or on your behalf in the course of your present or future dealings with Hulala Sdn Bhd (Company No. 1005279-U), its subsidiary(ies), its associated company(ies), its joint venture partners, including of all of its shareholder(s), its director(s), its employee(s), its supplier(s), its contractor(s) and/or its permitted person(s) ("we", "our", "us" or "Company"). Your personal data facilitates us to achieve the Purpose in clause 3 herein that are in connection with our business. 
  2. **Description of personal data**
    * The personal data that you will provide may include but not limited to your name, age, identity card number or passport number, address of correspondence, including office address, gender, date of birth, marital status, occupation, contact information, including e-mail address, mobile number, race, religion, nationality. 
  3. **Purpose**
    * The compilation and processing of personal data includes but not constrained to the following purposes: 
      * Promotions
        * We may use to send daily, weekly, monthly newsletters or deals information via reminder@news.hulala.com.my (Hulala Malaysia) based on your information such as email addresses or mobile that you provide to us
      * Services & Products
        * Delivery of our main services and products or products whether present or future;
        * Customer relationship management procedures whichever we deem necessary and fit;
        * Client profiling activities in connection with our services and products;
        * Interaction with you and delivery of information by e-mail, telecommunication means, including telephone calls or text messages or social media about products and services offered by us and/or our client(s);
        * Such other purposes provided for in our particular services or products offered by us and/or our client(s);
      * Internal Record & External (Marketing)
        * Marketing of our products and/or services to you whether present or future;
        * For purposes relating to any of the above, including but not constrained to research, benchmarking and statistical analysis;
        * Internal record keeping;
      * Legal Compliance
        * Prevention, hindrance, reporting of any crime including but not constrained to fraud, bribery and money laundering;
        * Compliance to any legal or regulatory requirements relating to the provision of our services and/or products and to make disclosure under the requirements of any applicable law, regulation, direction, court order, order, by-law, guideline, circular, code applicable to us or any associated, subsidiary, related companies of our group.
  4. **Sources**
    * The sources that we may obtain your personal data includes but not constrained to booking forms, registration forms, online forms, agreements you have signed, name cards or any identity materials that you have distributed voluntarily; and business directory(ies) or listing(s) that you have subscribed to share your information, etc.
  5. **Class of Third Parties**
    * Customarily, your personal data with us will be kept confidential. You hereby consent and authorize us to disclose your personal data to the following categories of third parties: 
      * our associated, subsidiary, related companies of the Company;
      * our business partners including online business affiliates, retailers, distributors, agents, merchant that provide, supply, distribute or deal in general with our services and/or products in connection with our business and in relation to our loyalty programs and other programs;
      * our auditors, business consultants, accountants, lawyers or other professional advisers and/or consultants as we deem necessary and appropriate;
      * to a local or state or federal authority, industry regulator, enforcement agency, statutory authority, court of laws, tribunal, arbitration centre, commission or council or association legally authorized by law.
  6. **Your Obligations**
    * It is obligatory for you to supply your personal data to us in the most accurate manner. Failing which, we are unable to process your personal data on your behalf and for the Purpose stated in clause 3 herein and all relationships created or to be created between us shall then be terminated and ceased to be in effect immediately. 
  7. **Your Rights**
    *       * Right to request access to personal data
        * You are entitled to request access to your personal data that is processed by us with reasonable notice. 
      * Right to request correction of personal data 
        * You are entitled to request access to your personal data that is processed by us with reasonable notice. 
          * request correction and/or update of your personal data that is inaccurate, incomplete or out-of-date; and
          * request retention of your personal data only as long as necessary for the fulfillment of the Purpose stated in clause 3 herein.
      * Rights to limit processing of your personal data
        * You are entitled to limit our processing of your personal data by expressly withdrawing in full, your consent given previously, in each case, including for direct marketing purposes subject to any applicable legal restrictions, contractual conditions and within a reasonable time period. 
  8. **Contact to make inquiries and complaints regarding personal data**
    * If you intend to exercise your rights in clause 7 or to make inquiries or complaints regarding your personal data, our policies, procedures in relation to processing your personal data, you may contact the relevant department at the end of the page.
  9. **Other information**
    * You may visit our website [www.hulala.com.my](http://www.hulala.com.my/) to learn more about our privacy policy.

## Disclosure of Your Information

We do not give information about you to government agencies, organisations or anyone else unless one of the following applies:   
Legal requirements   
Service providers or strategic partners that would help our business operations (such as payment provider for fraud cases, bill collection, affiliate programs, loyalty programs and co-branding activities) 

You told us to do so or we have seek authorization from you that we will.

It is related to criminal investigation or any legal activity that is require by any law enforcement bodies to assist their investigation.

Business Joint Venture or business merging or acquired by business entity. If there is an event or combination of event occur, we may combine their privacy policy practise with respect to your personal information. In such cases, you will be notify prior notice.

## Account Information Protection

Our staffs cannot see you password that you used in hulala website. Please do not disclose your password to anyone except the one that you have authorized to do so else you are solely responsible for any account information loss, vouchers used, cash back token and affiliate earning used. If you notice unusual activities pertaining your hulala account, notify us immediately for any necessary action.

® This User Agreement is the property of **Hulala Sdn. Bhd.** _(1005279-U)_ and may not be used or copied without permission.

**Customer Service Department**   
**Helpline :** 1700-81-5058 (9.30am – 6.00pm)   
**Email :** [support@hulala.com.my](mailto:support@hulala.com.my)   
42-2, Jalan Kuchai Maju 10, Kuchai Enterpreneur's Park, 58200 Kuala Lumpur. Malaysia
